No, no, I'm really glad you said that.
I feel like I'm popular on my own, yes.
Awww!
So it was a popular day at school.
Yes, it was.
Buddy.
Did you have a good time?
No, I did not.
Did you have fun?
Yes, I did.
I wanted to take Iwamoto off the stage so I could hear what you guys had to say.
Then he laughed so much, I was so happy!
On such a large scale, like that field sound...
And I think Buddy's is already showing off its cuteness now, but
But I think if we were to go out on stage with a flashy look, people would be even more pleased with us.
That would be great.
It's the royal road to the stage that I've been longing for since I was a kid.
I want to feel that.
I'm really excited about it.
I know it's not a surprise, but it's something new.
I think the live show is the place where we can offer new things to you.
I'm the oldest leader, 28 years old, and everybody loves me.
I love it so much, and it really helps me a lot.
We've never had a situation where we throw something at them and they come back to us with their voices.
I've been saying this for a long time, but it makes me really happy.
I'm so happy.
I'm deeply moved.
Thank you very much for your time.
Buddy's.
Buddy's show, please.
Yes, Buddy's show, please.
YABANA: Three days to go. Well, I'm a very focused person, so I have to do things just in time.
I'm not in a hurry to do it, but if I don't do it last minute, I can't do it, so I dare to concentrate on it 3 days before the show.
If I didn't understand a part, I would ask Fumi and Kumio to help me with the details, and then I would repeat it about 10 times to make sure I got it right.
Then, I would go to bed the next day and wake up to find that I was in.
I'm having a lot of fun dancing.
Dancing is fun.
To be honest, I like singing,
Dancing is something I always wanted to do,
I didn't get into this business because I wanted to dance,
I enjoy dancing,
I enjoy dancing, but it's just dancing.
If you ask me if I like dancing,
I don't like dancing.
Singing, dancing, and being cheered by people,
I like it all in general.
I just don't have confidence.
It's not that I don't like it.
Do you like dancing? I want to say I like it.
I don't dislike it.
I can dance. I can't dance.
I can't dance,
I can't say that because my dancing skill is out of proportion,
I can't say it. Like, "I love you.
But recently
But I like dancing regardless of that.
I like the way you and Fumiya pretend to be O-Light.
He invites me to do that, too.
I'm kind of happy.
If he asks me to do it...
I used to be like, "Are you serious?
Like, "I don't want to dance with a good dancer.
But now...
Fumiya teaches me how to dance, which I couldn't do before.
I'm happy that he's asking me out.
He said he felt I was having fun, so he invited me.
I can go to the forest.
He tells me to get dressed up.
Because of Kimihana's influence.
They all have dance experience.
They were all so cohesive, you know?
I went to see that kind of thing before we were buddies.
I'd go to other events and see people from other groups as well, and I'd see them.
Watlin is going to fall.
I thought, "Wow!
Everyone was doing it because they knew they couldn't lose.
Everyone is getting better.
Tapioca is also getting really good.
I think that's true.
It's... it's... it's... it's... it's...
And now we've got Magic and other new songs.
And we've got new songs.
We're all singing together now, right, with microphones.
And then...
I don't like it when I'm the only one singing.
Everyone should sing more melodies.
Everyone has their own personality.
Everyone's voice is different.
I don't want to sing in my own voice all the time.
I don't feel like it's fresh.
I wanted everyone to sing with a microphone.
That's why we practiced a lot.
Everyone sings.
And of course we practice dancing.
But I'm not a good singer.
I'm not a good singer, but I can show people
But if everyone sings...
I won't be able to stand up.
I have to do the same for the dancers.
I'm trying my best to keep up with them.
I've been having a bit of a hard time keeping up with the others lately.I've been having a bit of a bad day lately because I've been burning up with motivation for everyone else.
I'm kind of caught up in it.
I heard you've moved on.
Thank you for watching!
I know the members are good at dancing and singing.
We all have different strengths, but we all stand out in some way.
But we thought it would be better to make them stand out in some way.
Fumi and Shouto talked about it.
A group is called "main vocalist", but it's not the same as "buddies".
But everyone is the main singer of the group, and we're all buddies.
For example, there are people who are not my fans.
For example, Takuya fans, Sware fans.
There are people who like each other.
So when I think about all the fans
I think about the fans who are members of my precious group, Buddies.
I think it would be better for the fans if I could make them stand out more.
It would be nice if I was the only one and they were all my fans.
But that's definitely not the case.
There are a lot of different fans who come to see Buddies.
For the sake of those who come to see the show
I want to show them how good I am.
We all wanted to do our best to stand out from the crowd.
I don't know how to choreograph, I don't know how to dance.
They teach you how to step and stomp, and they teach you how to
And they teach us how to sing, and they teach us the rights and all that.
Everyone teaches me.
I feel like this is what we're trying to do to improve together.
But I am having a lot of fun, and I am getting a lot of inspiration from many people during this period,
I have received a lot of inspiration from many people during this period, so I feel as if I am managing it within the scope of a gift.
I hope I can show it in my performance.
This time, I don't care about the worldview anymore.
I would like to perform with the simple theme of "playing a role".
I would like to give a live performance with the simple theme of "creating a worldview".
As the sun goes down and it gets darker in the second half
The sun is going down and it's getting darker.
Well, the day is getting longer...
I'm really looking forward to the change in the sky.
I'm really looking forward to the change of the sky.
On an outdoor stage, daytime and nighttime are totally different.
I think it's a very rare opportunity to experience something like that.
I'd like to enjoy that as well.
I wonder what it will be like to hear my buddy's voice in the open air.
I wonder what it's like to hear my buddy's voice outdoors.
I honestly can't imagine what it will be like.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I've had a lot of opportunities to be on stage.
I've had a lot of opportunities to perform on stage.
I'm really looking forward to doing a one-man show again
I'm really excited to have another one-man show like this after Winterland.
I'm really excited about it and I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've been reevaluating my dancing and especially my singing during this period.
I hope I can show my growth in a way that is easy to understand.
There are a lot of things that are new to me this time.
I don't know, I have a lot of anxiety.
But now that I've actually done it, I'm really looking forward to it.
Well, well...
I'm getting more and more confident.
My dancing skills are getting better, and my singing skills are getting better, too.
I want to improve my dancing skills and my singing skills as well.
I want to be someone who can do that properly.
I actually got to see other groups perform at Pepare.
I've been doing a lot of research on that this year.
But still...
I don't know...
I think it's cool to see other groups like this.
I think it's cool to see them like this, of course.
But what I want to use as a reference is...
I'd like to refer to the members of Buddy's.
I don't know how to put it...
For example...
Simply in terms of dancing...
It's amazing.
Fumiya-san's movements are very graceful.
Or the movements between dances.
or a little ad-libbing like that.
I think SHO is very cool.
Or the way he sings.
And of course, KEVIN's singing...
I feel at ease when I listen to him.
The person who is performing also
I think the quality of his voice and the way he sings are cool.
I think it's cool.
Also, the Mori brothers often sing in a way that is unique to live performances.
I think it's cool to see them do that.
I was also influenced by other groups.
I am often inspired by the members of my own group.
The way Buddy's performs live...
I'm sure that all 10 members are cool in their own way.
I think that's the strength of this group.
I really feel that we try to be the coolest at that moment.
I really feel that I want to be the coolest at that moment.
That's why I want everyone to be the best they can be.
Everyone is really cool!
Please subscribe to my channel.
Seriously, all my fans are really nice.
Probably.
Definitely very kind.He's definitely kind.
He probably knows my personality.
Maybe I'm like, "Let's try it this way," or "Let's try it this way.
And then even once you say something like...
"Oh, that's weird.
Like, "Oh, that's a little bit weird. I'm like, "Oh, that's too weird.
I'll just go back to it and say, "Don't try it again.
That's why everyone should give it a try.
And they support me a lot, so I can do a lot of performances with peace of mind.
So I can do various performances with peace of mind.
It's really because of you guys.
I don't know.
Just as you said, they are looking after me so kindly.
That's for sure.
I can feel that, especially lately.
It's amazing to think that so many people
I'm so happy to think that so many people are giving me so much love.
I'm really happy to think that so many people are giving me so much love.
I've been trying to drink Genki Sokken before the show, so I hope you guys will drink it too.
Please bring Genki Hayakko with you so that we can all be energized together!
And one more thing, please bring your penlights if you can!
I know it's already on Youtube.
It would be fun if we can do this and that with everyone!
I'm sure the scenery will be beautiful outdoors.
I'd be happy if you could bring it!
And one last thing...
The last one...
The last thing I want you to bring.
Love.
Please bring lots of love.
I'll give it back double.
I'll give it back a hundredfold.
I will definitely satisfy you.
I think he knows I'm a little insecure.
Yes! Shall we go?
Hey!
Let's start at 3:00, mic check, guitar check, and then we'll go through.
Yes, please.
Then we'll take a break.
I'll do my best.
Okay, here we go.
All right.
What's this?
That's the course at pickup tuck.
I'm doing pickup tacks, but I can't do that part.
Wait a minute.
One's in danger.
I was like, "Why is milk so good?
I couldn't react.
Oh no, it's so hard to eat. I forgot how to eat it.
So cute!
Too cute!
It's too cute!
When you say so, when you say so...
It makes me happy to be told that.
Like old times, old times.
You don't have to say it twice. When they say it, they say it.
You don't have to say it twice.
You know, you're in the ocean, and you're out on a hairy stretch of beach.
We'll go down about 30 meters.
You can do it, right?
Sideways, sideways, no problem.
Can you do it horizontally?
No, not horizontally, no way.
You can do 30 meters horizontally?
Where are you going to kick it the second time after you've kicked it once?
Awwwwwww!
Right, and the kemagure is, the kemagure is over here.
So what if we do a spurtle in the forest in the ocean?
In the forest?
Humans float when there's air here, air here, air in their bodies.
Awwwwwww!
That's why we drop the air once inside the body.
It's dead, it's dead, it's dead, it's dead!
Let it go, let it go, let it go
It sinks in a state of crying, but it comes somewhere else
Awww, awww, awww.
That's what this is, Meaty Kip, that's what this is.
Awwwww!
This, these days, we're rapidly going to more events than ever before, we're going to more events than ever before.
So, I've had a lot of experiences, you know, like playing with other artists and so on, so I've kind of grown up a little bit.
I think I've grown up a little bit.
I think I have grown up a little, including my confidence in performing on stage.
After performing with other artists
After playing live with other artists
It's totally different when we do our own one-man show after performing with other artists.
It feels like a home away from home.
It's like a home away from home or a friendly feeling.
I think that's one of the charms of a one-man show.
I think that's the charm of one-man shows.
But this time Kevin couldn't make it.
I'm sure that must be frustrating for you.
I've missed a show once before.
I was in the first place.
I know how you feel.
I know how frustrating it must be for you.
to Kevin's luck.To Kevin's luck, while feeling the
I really hope I can do my best in my performance.
The next day is my birthday
I'll be waiting for your congratulatory messages.
See you soon!
Three days to go, yes, it's early.
Also, since Kevin is not here, we are going to perform with 9 members this time,
I will carry Kevin's feelings with me, and I will do it with the feeling that Kevin is there.
Also, this is the first time to perform outdoors, so I would like to deliver power to the people in the back of the venue.
I hope you can enjoy the show while breathing the air and feeling the temperature.
The show starts a little late, like 5:00 pm.
So, I think the songs will have the feel of songs in the dark,
I'm glad you enjoyed the atmosphere of the venue and the world of the song,
I would be happy if you could enjoy the world of the songs and the atmosphere of the venue.
I would like to improve my performance, and I would like to do more rapping,
I would also like to improve my dance performance and singing.
I have been downgraded from magic to singing,
I want to improve my singing ability, which is all included in the performance aspect,
I would like to gradually improve my singing ability.
Please do that quite a bit.
At the live concert, all the empty memories here will be engraved here.
It's been six months since I last performed here.
We put a lot of energy into this one-man show, rehearsing every day.
We rehearsed every day and put a lot of energy into it, but Kevin noticed, so we performed with just the nine of us.
We wanted to deliver the message to Kevin, and we also wanted everyone to have a good time.
So please be careful and come to the venue, and let's have fun together.
I'll be waiting for you.
We've been working on this project pretty much last minute, and we've been working on it a few times.
We were able to go through the whole thing the day before yesterday, and it's all pretty well organized now.
But since it's an open-air concert, you can't really see it, and since it's a never-before-seen fan-man concert, there are still some things you can't see.
We'll rehearse on the day of the show and get ready for the show.
I have a goal for this show, and of course I want to show my feelings in the open air, and I have a goal for every show.
But this time, I want to put my feelings into the outdoor performance.
If your mind is moved by your feelings, you can't do it.
I want to be careful with my dance moves and singing as well.
This time, I want to dance and use my head, paying attention to the tips of my fingers until the very end.
I have a goal to perform with my head in mind.
The way the sound resonates.
The way the sound resonates and the reverberation of the song is totally different.
But the good thing about Buddies is that it can only be performed outdoors.
I think the energy of Baddies can only be expressed in the open air.
I think the energy of Buddies comes alive outdoors.
I hope we can bring that energy to everyone.
This will be our first outdoor concert, so let's get excited!
I'd be happy if you could come to the show with care.
Now, let me introduce the technique of my partner
Let me introduce you to my partner's technology.
Hello everyone, please.
I'm Wise.
Um, uh, yes, please!
Um, from here to, um, until the end of Osaka.
One chuukko, crane pose.
Oh, I got it!
Yes, sir!
Okay, yeah,
Ten crane poses.
You're gonna be the key head of the event, dude.
I'll dye it for you.
Well, well, it's been six months.
I haven't been to an event in six months.
There's been a lot going on, but...
But it's been a while.
I thought while rehearsing
It's been a while since I've felt like this.
And after we did the rehearsal, as everyone said...
It's pretty packed.
It's pretty hard.
So this time
Well, you know...
Of course we want to entertain, but we also want to challenge ourselves to improve our skills and performance ability.
I think that if we can get through this one more time, we will be able to improve our skills and performance ability.
And also, you know, people might be worried about Capa Kevyn, but, you know, I tweeted about it.
I've tweeted about it, but we're still the same 10 members, and we'll take it to the stage regardless of that.
We are talking about performing as a group of 10.
What is our next goal?
The world will know about Buddies.
And also, I'd like to build up the relationship between the members even more.
We're going to build on that even more.
That kind of bond between the members.
Even if we leave family aside, the people we spend the most time with are the members of the group.
From now on in our lives, we are the members of the band.
And when we meet each other, we can be together for the rest of our lives.
I want to make a group that I can be with for the rest of my life, so that's what I'm trying to do.
I want to make a group that we can be together for the rest of our lives when we meet.
If we can become good friends, work friends...
I think that's what I've been thinking about the most lately.
No, seriously, I'm going to do it. I'm really going to do it.
I'll be really serious.
I want to show you all how cute I am, so please check it out!
I'm going to do it by myself today.
I mean, there's a goal I've been setting for myself lately, and it's a personal one.
I'm going to dance as hard as I can regardless of the fact that I can't sing anymore.
But of course I'll give it my all when I sing.
I don't want to focus too much on singing.
I've recently developed a desire to dance anyway.
I've been participating in various events, such as the platform version, and I'm really inspired by it.
That's why I want to sing, dance, and do everything.
I also want to rap.
I want to give my all in everything I do.At any rate, I want to give my all in everything I do.
No matter what the outcome, no matter what I regret.
I'm sure we'll really give it our all.
I'm looking forward to it. It'll be my first time outdoors.
I'm sure we'll make it a great memory no matter if it rains or not.
You can rest assured that we will make it a great memory for sure.
I'm going to miss Kemiko's voice.
I felt a lot of pressure today.
My brother and I sang the chorus together.
The three of us sang the chorus part together, and the rest will appear on the soundtrack.
And the rest will be on the soundtrack.
I saw the reality through the microphone today.
I saw it through the microphone.
I want to show everyone who is watching that
I want to show them that we are doing this with all our backs to the audience.
I want to put that pressure off.
The group is where I grew up, so it's like a family.
I'm having fun.
And I want everyone to have fun.
I want everyone to have fun, and I want everyone to have fun, but I also want everyone to have the same goal, which is to go bar-b- bar-bar-bar to this place.
I want everyone to have the same goal, the same vector.
If we do that, we can definitely be happy.
I can see that in my mind.
All we have to do now is to do our best to entertain our fans and deliver our music in our own way.
and deliver our music in our own way.
I hope you will support us freely.
I want to do my best so that I'll be standing in a big place before I know it.
I want to do my best.
But really...
I'm really serious.
Laughs
Yes, as we do more and more gigs
The more we do live shows, the more everyone's spirits get stronger and stronger.
Of course, I have great memories from each show.
But as each show goes on...
the way everyone faces each song.
the way we faced each and every song.
the more I feel that everyone is getting more and more serious
I can feel it more and more.
I really enjoy feeling that.
I think we've been doing a lot of live shows
I think we've been doing a lot of live shows, valuing the "buddies" style.
We've been doing a lot of live shows, but this is the first time we're doing volume 5, and we're in our third year, so it's our first show this year.
It's the first time for us to do a live show, so it's an opportunity for us to change our mindset.
I feel like it's an opportunity to change my mind.
We are going to polish our skills and other things more than before.
This live show is a time when we all want to go further.
We still have a lot of issues to work on.
But I think it's important for all of us to be able to aim for that.
We have a secret theme that we don't tell everyone.
Like, "This is the kind of live we're going to do this time.
I think it's important for Bandeis to have this kind of live show.
I think it's important to have a live show where we are in this position
We all decide together what we want to do at each show.
We talk about this kind of thing so that we can grow with each show.
We are talking about this kind of thing.
We're all working towards this goal.
I don't know.
I don't know, we're working on it seriously.
More than ever before.
I feel a sense of accomplishment when we succeed.
I felt like we were going in the direction we wanted to go, judging from the way we performed today.
I'm too impressed.
I don't know what to say.
I think it's a live show where you can really get everyone involved.
I think we'll be able to speak a lot more than usual.
I think we'll be able to speak a lot more than usual
I think I can dance a lot.
I think I can dance a lot, and I've made a lot of that part of the show.
And there will also be a section where
I hope to show Buddies again.
I'm thinking about how it would be nice to do a song like this at sunset.
I'm working on it while thinking about it.
But even if I don't...
But even if it's not, that's interesting too, isn't it?
For example, it might rain.
Even if it rains.
That's one of the memories.
It's only possible outdoors.
It's just the way it is.
We used to support each other, but now it's like...
For example, we had everyone dancing to what I or Fumi had made.
That was our good point, but
But we're getting more and more choreographers and so on.
Yuta-san has been doing the music and so on.
By asking different people to do things for us
By doing this, we can all do our best for this project.
I think it made us all more aware of the importance of doing our best for this project.
I feel like we've all become more aware that we have to do our best on this task together.
The wall that we all share
There is no barrier that stands in the way of all of us.
That's right.
I feel that the 10 of us are all the same, and we are all working together now.
I feel that we are all working together more than before.
In that sense.
[ED
I don't know...
Well, I've been doing a lot of Buddies' performances.
I've been doing a lot of demonstrations with Buddies, and I've noticed that my performances and our songs really bring smiles to people's faces and make them work harder tomorrow.
I don't know, I knew it, but I felt like there must be people who can do their best tomorrow.
I've been able to support everyone up to this point.I've really learned and felt how much support we have from everyone.
I really learned and felt that we can feel everyone's presence so much.
That's the most shocking thing about this activity.
I want to get bigger, but I'd rather be that kind of presence for more people.
I would like to expand the circle of such a supportive and supportive environment.
Personally, I want to be a person who can support each other in terms of ability as a group.
I want to be a person who can support the group in terms of ability.
But most of all, I want to be a group that can be a part of everyone's daily life.
I don't want to be a distant presence.
What we are doing now is exactly what we want to do.
I want to expand this more and more.
We don't have to forgive anything.
I think it would be nice to have some goods.
Yes, well, I really think
I'm really looking forward to seeing Buddy's
I think it's going to be a big stage for Buddies.
I think it's going to be a big stage for us.
Let's just have fun together.
I'm really looking forward to it.
It won't be for another 6 months.
Let's have fun together!
Don't waste time
You are beautiful
Damn, you are beautiful
Don't tell me you don't know
Na na na na na na
So you give me love, give me love, babe
So you give me love, give me love
You are beautiful
I love you already
Give it up
You are beautiful
So you're beautiful